団長に伝えてくれ。
Looks like you guys have been
waiting here to kill me.
俺は　鎖野郎とケリをつけるまでは 帰れねえとな。
Sorry, but the prey is about
to become the predator. You'll die before you can even strike back.
団長は　獲物をひとしきり愛でると 全て売り払う。 緋の眼も例外ではないはずだ。
Grudge x And x Dread
それ以上のことは知らない。
Your bodies can't keep up with your minds...
１つ言えることは
You obviously can't compete physically.
頭を潰さない限り 「クモ」は動き続ける。
How are you gonna compensate? With guns? Numbers?
さっき　組むかと聞いたが 一蓮托生ってわけじゃ　ない。
We'll use wit and experience.
情報交換を基本とした ギブ　アンド　テークだ。 互いの条件が合わなければ
Where did this stuff come from?
それ以上の協力は無理強いなし。
Smoke? Gas? Poison gas?
気楽だろ？
Or sleeping gas?
返答は？
No, they're standing within it.
明日　また同じ時間に。
This must be some kind of special power. Are you scared?
で　これから　どうする？ 恐らく　リーダーは死んだ。
Then this is a smokescreen. They'll use it as cover for their attack.
任務も遂行できてないし…。
Well, let's see what they can do...
ボスに報告しなくていいの？
Here it comes!
ボスとは名ばかりの ただの子供だぜ。 他に本当の雇い主がいる。 えっ？
What?
実際の指示は彼が出して
When you use Gyo, your body freezes briefly.
それをリーダーが受けていたんだ。
This trick won't work on the same
opponent too many times.
リーダー以外は 連絡先も知らないがな。
But it only needs to once.
どちらにしろ ボスに報告するしかないだろう。 ボス…　ボス。
I wouldn't be so sure. That didn't hurt at all. I'll admit that you caught me off-guard, but you didn't do any damage.
ん？
What's this?
今　何時？ 夜中の２時です。
Gee, I wonder... It's time.
え！　じゃあ　競売は？
Adding interest.
中止になりました。
Answer me.
えっ？　中止？　何で？
Answer me!
競売会場が盗賊に襲われました。 えっ？ その際に　ヴェーゼ　イワレンコフ トチーノの３名が殉職しました。
Your anger is blinding you
to your surroundings...
えっ!? リーダーも連絡がとれず 恐らく彼も…。
It'll be super easy to send you tumbling.
うそ…。 じゃあ　「ミイラ」は？ ん？
Hey! Damn it!
ホントに盗まれちゃったの？ 絶対　欲しかったのに。
They're gone? Where are you?
競売品は　コミュニティーが 安全な場所へ移したようです。
It's time. Adding interest.
まだ分かりません。 え　何で？
It doesn't matter what your power does.
とにかく　全ての連絡網は リーダーが把握していたので
I just have to rip you apart!
私だって分かんないよ そんなこと。
Looks like he's powerless against Zetsu.
じゃあ　パパに聞いて。 ケータイに番号入ってるから。
Well, we're dealing with
a level-one soldier ant.
スクワラ　電話してくれ。 えっ？　何で俺だよ！
With APR on him, we can easily track him.
この中では お前が一番の古株だろ？
We just need to chase him down,
box him in, and that'll be the end.
お前がリーダーに…。 無理だ！　無理　無理！ 俺は　とても リーダーなんて柄じゃ　ねえ。
But doesn't your ability lose its effect
if the target moves too far away?
全員で決めたらどうかしら？ 公平に。
It'll stop adding interest, but the effect will remain.
とにかく 早く連絡したほうがいい。
Once I'm back in range,
the counter will start up again.
私はクラピカを推すわ。
But even if IRS doesn't kick in,
he'll be easy to finish off.
賊を捕らえたのも彼だし 適切な判断力もあると思う。
We've already learned his attacks. You fool!
この中では 一番　適任じゃないかしら。 異議なし　俺もクラピカに１票。
We may know what pitch he'll use, but we still can't put the bat on the ball.
決まりだ　お前がやってくれ。
Let's leave him for a Nen user who's
better equipped to handle him. You're right.
分かった…　とにかく代理として ノストラード氏に連絡する。
I'm more concerned about Gon and Killua...
確認されるまでの間だ。
Damn...
最終的な判断は ノストラード氏にしてもらおう。
I can't shake this thing. I can't outrun it...
こんなに早く チャンスが来るとは…
So this is Nen. I need more than just speed here.
[TEL]　ええ。 信じられんな 彼は念能力者だぞ。
Kite's in here.
[TEL] 銃弾１０発　食らっても
He is no longer the person you once knew.
平気なくらいの鍛え方は しているはずだが。
It's okay.
相手が「幻影旅団」という 盗賊なんです。
We'll find a way to cure him!
[TEL]　間近で戦闘を見ましたが
Hotel Rafflesia...
連中の１人は バズーカ砲を片手で防ぎました。 私は代理の クラピカという者ですが
Once I've dealt an enemy a
certain amount of damage, I'm able to trap
これから　どうするべきか 指示を頂けませんか？ まず　代理としての 君の考えを聞こうか。
an entire body or merely a single part inside.
[TEL]　娘さんを　一刻も早く
This must be how he took my eye.
分かった 今　俺も　そっちへ向かっていて 明日の夕方には着く。
If I release him from the cage,
he'll return to his original size.
ネオンは 何とか俺が説得してみよう。
Be careful.
[TEL]　リーダーは君が継げ クラピカ。
He cannot use Nen, but he is still strong.
あ！
Most likely, they used him to train soldiers.
これか！
He automatically attacks
anyone who approaches.
ヨークシン付近で所有してる 物件が分かるか？ もちろん！
Kite...
ついでに　最近　組員名義での 宿泊者がいないかも調べよう。
It's okay now. It's okay.
出た あのビルの他に所有物件が２つ。
It's been a while... since you punched me.
まぁ　こいつらなら すぐに見つかるんじゃない？ サンキュー　恩に着るぜ！
That hurt a lot...
死体の始末はつけとく。 早くケリつけて来い。 おう！
You're going to let this beating continue?
じゃあ！ ウボォー！
Gon can't use Nen to defend himself either, right?
あ？ 油断禁物だよ。
It's okay, Gon will notice.
ああ。
Maybe he already has, and is still...
構成員か… こいつらから当たってみるか
He's suppressing his reflexes to dodge or block, allowing himself to be hit.
これを見てくれ。 これは！ ノストラードファミリーの 所有物件リスト？
But Gon shouldn't be able to adapt
so quickly in his current state!
構成員のリストまで…。 まさか　こんな情報が…。
I'm sure he doesn't know what else to do.
これは　プロハンター専用の 情報サイトだ。 この情報をたどれば
This is the reality we've created
that we must now face.
我々のいる　この部屋も 突き止めることができる。 プロハンター専用サイト…。
He'll go right next.
じゃあ　もし敵にも プロハンターがいたら…。 非常にマズい。
Right again. And then left.
今すぐ　ボスを連れて 別の部屋を借りてくれ。
Then a feint...
下手に移動するより早いからな ただし　偽名はダメだ。
He really does fight like a robot. Kite isn't this weak...
センリツか バショウの名前で登録しろ。
Kite's punches
ボスもみんなも　絶対に その部屋から出ないように。
hurt much more!
お…　恐らく　そいつは 組員じゃなく
Get some rest.
組長の娘のボディーガードだ。
We'll take it from here.
占い？
Level two...
マフィアの中に 顧客が大勢いて コミュニティーの長老にも 信奉者がいるそうだ　ハハハ…。
Gon can't see that thing, but it activates when anyone touches Kite.
ほう。 何しろ　うちの組長は
You must be highly skilled at
combat to clear this test.
娘の占いのおかげで 出世したようなもんだからな。 なっ！　頼む！
I've already blocked Kite's Nen, so that belongs to whoever's controlling him.
これだけ話したんだ！ 助けてくれ…！
Be careful.
予知能力者がいたか…
What do I do? How did you stop him?
そいつに襲撃は 読まれていたってことか
We injured him badly.
やっぱり　団長が正しかった 俺達の中に裏切り者は　いねえ
We had no choice, but I'm still sorry. If you stay away, he won't attack.
締めて 約８００万の予算がある。 何とか　これを 『グリードアイランド』の最低落札価格
Kite... Just wait a little longer.
９０億以上まで 増やさなきゃいかんわけだが やはり　まっとうな方法じゃ とても届かねえ金額だ。
I'll get you back to normal soon.
いいんだよ　それで。
Killua...
えっ？ えっ？ できるだけ　尾ひれが ついてたほうが　ありがたい。 どういうこと？
I want that one myself!
モグラ？　そんなもん捕まえて どうするの？
Killua... I knew something was different when I saw you.
うるせぇな 今　ゆっくり説明してやっから。 さぁ　いらっしゃい！
What did you guys do in the
short time since I saw you last?
条件競売だよ！
We didn't do anything.
競売品は ３００万相当のダイヤモンド！ 落札条件は　腕相撲！
Our enemies did.
この少年に勝った者に ダイヤが与えられますよ！
A Few Weeks Later
参加費用は１万ジェニー！ 何だ？　子供だぜ！ やってみるか！
Twenty-nine days have passed
since Gon lost his Nen.
やめとけ　あのガキ　昨日 ５００人抜きやった　つわものだ。 えっ!?
Are you sure we should let them come along?
腕を折られた奴も ２０人以上いたそうだぜ。
We'll be breaking our promise to the old man.
ホントかよ…。
I see no problem with that.
ヘへっ　いい感じで 噂が独り歩きしてるぜ
The test was to determine
who would enter NGL...
これなら… どけ。
And we are headed to the
Republic of East Gorteau.
おっ！　早速　挑戦ですか？
Sounds like a technicality to me.
そうじゃ　ねえ！ あ？
Then you think we shouldn't bring them with us?
こいつじゃ　その小僧に 勝てないのは知ってる。
No, they're grown tigers now.
昨日　見てたからな。 だったら　何でしょう？ もっと　もうけたくないか？
They can take care of themselves.
…というと？ こんな所で　ちまちま稼ぐより もっと大きな勝負が
I would agree that Killua is capable, but what about Gon?
できる場所がある。
At the very end, I was impressed
by the way he moved.
ここで稼ぐ何百倍 いや　何千倍にもなるぜ。 ニッヒッヒ。
But he hasn't shown any fire since. And he clearly isn't focused during training.
この２人がモグラなの？
I believe his performance is quite inconsistent.
ああ　かかった魚は　デカそうだぞ。 えっ　魚？　モグラでしょ？
But he's consistently inconsistent.
うるせぇな どっちでもいいんだよ。
He only gets serious when he absolutely must.
ここだ。
I think his lack of drive these past few
weeks will actually give him a boost.
このアームレスリングは 無差別の賞金制だ。
What is the agenda behind
the sudden flurry of activity
試合ごとに賭けが行われ　勝者には 賭け金の１０％が支払われる。
recently observed in East Gorteau?
１回の試合で動く金は億単位だ。
Supreme Leader Diego has personally invited
ってことは　１回　勝てば １０００万単位！ 場合によっては　もっとだ 紹介料として
all citizens to gather in the capital city, Peijing, to celebrate the
nation's birth in ten days.
俺は取り分の５０％を頂く。
Yes, there have been occasions
in the past during which
５０％？　取り過ぎじゃねえか？
all citizens were invited to participate.
俺の紹介がなきゃ参加できねえぞ それに　お前も賭ければいい。 その小僧ならオッズも上がって 元手が１００倍以上になるぜ。 なるほど　乗った！ 行け！　ゴン！
However, we've never seen
anything on this scale, where practically every citizen, from babies to the ill, has been summoned
for a celebration spanning three days.
えっ？ さぁ　次の対戦者は　いないか？
The logical conclusion would be that
the goal this time is different.
ここにいるぜ！
What do you believe the goal to be?
この小僧が挑戦する。
Well, it would send a powerful message
うん　いいだろう！ ん？
if he were to announce his successor
and abdication simultaneously.
突然ではありますが
But I find it hard to imagine the Supreme
Leader relinquishing his power.
アームレスリングは 中止させていただき これより　条件競売を 始めさせていただきます！
It may also be meant to distract
from some other matter.
え！ 中止って　どうなってんだよ！ いや　俺にも分からん。
In any event, the whole world will be
watching East Gorteau in ten days.
この競売条件は かくれんぼでございます！ かくれんぼ？
Next... Colt believes the celebration
will be used as a screening.
まずは プリントをお配りします！ 配られた プリントの写真をご覧ください！
We don't know what they'll do
with those found to have Nen, but ninety-nine percent of
the humans there will die.
そこに写った７名の男女が 今回のターゲットでございます！
We must stop it before that happens!
おい　このメガネのコ　確か…。
Our time limit is ten days.
うん　腕相撲に来てた！
What's the old man up to?
おい　こいつら もしかしたら昨夜の事件の？ ああ！　地下競売が 襲われたって　あれか？
He sent an e-mail saying that he's
already inside East Gorteau, but I haven't heard from him since.
あ…。
Do you think he's been taken out?
落札条件は　ターゲットを捕獲し 我々に引き渡すこと！ そうすれば ターゲット１名につき ２０億ジェニーの小切手と 交換させていただきます！
If he fails to contact us today, we've been told to assume as much.
期限は　ございません！ ターゲットの生死も問いません！
Speak of the devil, it's the Chairman.
捕らえ次第　ご連絡ください！
That old man's got some sharp ears...
１人２０億!?
He already knows everything.
全員　捕まえりゃ１４０億だぞ！
Including the fact that you boys are here.
参加費用として ５００万ジェニー　頂きます！
And that Morel-san is badmouthing him.
当然　参加だよな？ うん。
Divide into three pairs and draw the
Royal Guard away from the King.
あぁ　そうだ これからファクスする ネットで情報を集めろ 有力な情報には金を出す！
From the sharp-eared old man. That guy really scares me...
俺達も急ごうぜ。 慌てなくても　あんな連中にゃ 捕まえられないよ。
I'm sorry to say that your thirty days are up.
え？ え？ 何しろ　マフィアでさえ 手を焼いてんだから。
So I'll make myself scarce!
どういうことだ？ 条件競売だって言いながら まるっきし賞金首捜しだろ？
See you around... Bye!
つまり　マフィアが自分らの力で 捕まえられないって 認めてるようなもんじゃないか。
Okay, now you can use Nen again.
そういや　そうだな 予定を変更してでも
Give it a try.
こいつらを捜す必要が生じた。 さっき聞いたけど　昨夜 地下競売が襲われたらしい。
Gon... Sorry, but I'm still not convinced
we should keep you around.
地下競売が!?
Show me your resolve.
まさか　こいつらが…。
Attack me as if I were responsible for Kite.
それで盗っ人の首に 賞金を懸けたのか！ そう　マフィアのお宝　盗むなんて 頭イカレてるだろ。
If your attack is too weak, we'll replace
you with another Hunter.
でも　俺達は そんな連中の心当たりがある。
Seriously, the master can be so difficult. He already agreed to bring Gon along...
「幻影旅団」！
Gon, show him your Jajanken.
そういえば　クラピカは どうしてるんだろう？
You want me to attack you for real?
確かに…　もう来ているはずなのに 連絡が全然ないな。 電話してみよう。
Don't insult me! If you hold back in the slightest,
you're off the team!
[TEL]
Got it.
緋の眼を追ってるんだから 当然　闇の要人だよな。 その人の護衛で　地下競売に行って 事件に巻き込まれたのかも。
First comes rock...
[TEL]
Gon, that's enough...
１人か…　感心だな。
I was really about to kill you!
どこで死ぬ？ 好きな所で殺してやるよ。
You got me... You got me good.
ひとに迷惑が　かからない 荒野がいいな。
You go crazy with the best of them. We'll split up now.
お前の断末魔は　うるさそうだ。
Use whatever means you deem
best to fulfill your mission.
自身のプライドに泥を塗られた 借りを返しに現れたウボォーギン
Gon and Killua, as you requested,
you're assigned to Neferpitou.
そして　「幻影旅団」への 復讐のため
Knuckle and Shoot, you're on the
one called Menthuthuyoupi.
待ち受けていた　クラピカ
Knov and I will take Shaiapouf.
２人の戦いが　今　始まる！
Best of luck to you.